So friends, if you also want to insure your bike, that is, you
want to insure your vehicle, then
in today's video I am going to tell you step by step
that you
can insure your vehicle while sitting at home. Yes friends,
for this you do not need to go anywhere.
Today I am going to tell you this trick in this video. You have to
show all the steps
which I am going to explain step by step in today's video.
So let's
start the video. For this, you have to
come to the screen of your mobile or computer and
open whichever browser you use. As soon as
your browser opens,
you simply have to type 'Policy Bazaar' in the search bar
and then search it.
Now as you search it,
some such interface will open in front of you which you
can see here. First of all,
you have to click on the
link www.com.
Now as you do this, you will
come to its official website, you
can see it here. Its official website will appear to you in this
way. Now you
get many options here below which you can find
term life insurance.
You can find many insurances
here for insurance of car and health insurance, so you can see here,
in the fourth and fifth number you get the
option of car insurance and two wheeler insurance, etc. If you
want to do insurance of any type, then
click on the car option, if you
want to do bike insurance, then
you have to click on the two wheeler insurance option,
now as you click on it,
some such interface will open in front of you
where first of all you have to
type the number of your bike, so let's
type the bike number from here, after that
click on the option with price,
after that an option comes here
that your policy which has expired, if your
policy has expired, how many days it has
expired, then select it here,
after that another option will come in front of you from
where you are asked whether your
previous policy which has expired is of the first
name of this third party, then you will
select it from here, as soon as you click on it,
which company's
policy do you want to do, the
name of the job company will be shown in front of you,
now whichever company's policy you want to do  If you want, then
you will click on it from here and
you can also see here how much amount you are going to pay, if you scan here then
you get many more companies,
whichever company's insurance you
want to do, click on it, so here
friends I am going to show you the insurance of Bajaj company,
so let us
click on it, now after clicking on it you have to
fill the personal details,
first of all you have to choose Tiger,
after that type the owner name, the name of the person in whose name the
RC paper is, you will type it here,
in the option below you have to type the mobile number,
after that type the email ID which should be
your active email ID, after your policy is
generated the PDF file is
sent to your mail, so whatever email
ID you type, it should be your active email ID,
after that you have to type your address
and then select the district and your state,
in the option below
you have to type your pin code,
you have to click on the continue to step two first option,
after that this is in front of you  The
tattoo option will appear or now you have to
type the name normally from here,
whoever you want to enter normally, you will
type his name here,
so after typing this name from here,
you have to select the nominee relationship,
after that you have to type it normally
and then click on the option of continue to step three, from
here the stepfree
option will appear from where the registration
number and chassis number, engine number and
registration date of shop or lady will be
filled, now what you have to do is
click on the option of 747, now as soon as you
click on it, you will come to the final page
from where you will have to make the payment,
you will check your details once in the personal details here,
if all your details are
okay then you will click on the option of happy and take care,
friends, if you
want to make any correction in your details then
this is an option, you
can also correct your details by clicking on it, now friends, you
can also see the amount here, how much is your total amount going to be after
taking individual etc.
You will also be shown Amazon from here and
then you get one more option if you
want to set your P&A cover in this, then
you get the option here, if you
click on it then this amount will also be
added to your policy amount, from here
you can also take your P&A cover if you
want to take it, if you do not want to take it then
you will click on the option of opening an agency, then the
option of choose payment mode will appear in front of you from where you
will make your payment, for making payment you will
get the option of debit card or credit card or net banking UPI and Violet,
you will choose whichever way you want to make your payment easily, from
here friends I am going to make payment by credit card,
so I
click on the credit card option, you can make
your payment by clicking on whichever you like,
now you have to type the card number here,
so you have to type the Shukra number,
after that Neem Mohan card, the
name which is on your card, you have to type it
and then enter the expiry date,
enter the CVV code and then click on the pay option, as soon as you
click on this, your
account  An OTP will be sent to the mobile number linked to it,
you have to type that OTP here, by
clicking on it your
payment will be done, you can see here that the
process is a bit slow, right now
you have to wait for a few seconds here, so here
friends you can see that finally the payment has been made
and the policy number has been issued, to
download it you will get the option below,
download policy, simply you have to
click on this option, so the
PDF file of your policy will be
downloaded, you have to take a printout of it,
so friends from this side you can do your two
wheeler, car or four wheeler policy
online sitting at home in a very good way, I
hope you liked the video,
like and
share it and do not forget to subscribe to the channel,
friends, see you in the next video, till then
Jai